let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is the author of the classic science fiction novel Dune?",
        answer: "D. Frank Herbert",
        options: [
            "A. Isaac Asimov",
            "B. Philip K. Dick",
            "C. Arthur C. Clarke",
            "D. Frank Herbert"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "In which science fiction TV series does the starship USS Enterprise play a central role?",
        answer: "A. Star Trek",
        options: [
            "A. Star Trek",
            "B. Battlestar Galactica",
            "C. The Expanse",
            "D. Firefly"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which famous sci-fi film features a character named HAL 9000, an artificial intelligence computer?",
        answer: "C. 2001: A Space Odyssey of 1968",
        options: [
            "A. Blade Runner",
            "B. The Matrix",
            "C. 2001: A Space Odyssey of 1968",
            "D. War of the Worlds"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who wrote the dystopian novel 1984, a classic of science fiction literature?",
        answer: "B. George Orwell",
        options: [
            "A. Aldous Huxley",
            "B. George Orwell",
            "C. Ray Bradbury",
            "D. H.G. Wells"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "In the movie The Matrix, what is the real name of the protagonist who goes by the alias Neo?",
        answer: "B. Thomas A. Anderson",
        options: [
            "A. John Smith",
            "B. Thomas A. Anderson",
            "C. Kevin Johnson",
            "D. William Adams"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Who is the God of the sky and is considered the ruler, protector and father of all gods and humans?",
        answer: "C. Zeus",
        options: [
            "A. Hades",
            "B. Poseidon",
            "C. Zeus",
            "D. Hermes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which Greek hero is known for his incredible strength and the twelve labors he performed?",
        answer: "D. Hercules",
        options: [
            "A. Perseus",
            "B. Achilles",
            "C. Theseus",
            "D. Hercules"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Who is the goddess of wisdom, courage, and strategic warfare in Greek mythology?",
        answer: "B. Athena",
        options: [
            "A. Aphrodite",
            "B. Athena",
            "C. Artemis",
            "D. Demeter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What creature, half-man and half-bull, resided in the labyrinth of King Minos in Greek mythology?",
        answer: "A. Minotaur",
        options: [
            "A. Minotaur",
            "B. Centaur",
            "C. Harpy",
            "D. Chimera"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which mythological hero is known for his journey to the Underworld to rescue his wife, Eurydice?",
        answer: "A. Orpheus",
        options: [
            "A. Orpheus",
            "B. Perseus",
            "C. Odysseus",
            "D. Jason"
        ]
    },
];